{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","address":"24 W Adams","zipcode":"48226","owner":null,"licenseNumber":"224668","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/19/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E61000002CD5818348C354C0B8BE65741E2B4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"41596","establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","inspectionDate":"2018-02-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"1","pfcount":"5","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"6","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"6","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41596","inspectionDate":"2/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"41596","inspectionDate":"2/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"41596","inspectionDate":"2/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."},{"inspectionid":"41596","inspectionDate":"2/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Drainage system","subItem":"drain lines","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"inspectionid":"41596","inspectionDate":"2/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"41596","inspectionDate":"2/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"41596","inspectionDate":"2/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."},{"inspectionid":"41596","inspectionDate":"2/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"41596","inspectionDate":"2/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink bar","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"41596","inspectionDate":"2/27/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622694","name":"The Annex","violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"BAR (MAIN)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-03-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622694"}}